Nicholas McClure

86 Fieldgate Dr. Brantford ON, N3P 1H4

(647) - 913 - 6621

nicholasjmcclure@yahoo.ca nickjmcclure11@gmail.com

ABOUT ME

My name is Nicholas McClure and I am a 19 year old College Student who is about to finish my Second (2nd) year at Sheridan College for Computer Programming. Some of my interests include cooking, programming, and camping. I was an Army Cadet for 3 years and it is here that I developed a sense of leadership and the benefit of working in a team.

EXPERIENCE

Wendy's, Burlington — *Grill / General Worker*May 2021 - September 2022

Wendy's, Brantford — *Grill / General Worker*

May 2023 - September 2023

I worked as the store's main grill worker. I was tasked with preparing all of the protein, helping with sandwiches, cleaning all the fryers and grill, cleaning bathrooms, getting rid of the garbage, closing the store, and opening the store for breakfast.

St Teresa of Calcutta, Oakville — *Stage Crew*

March 2019 - June 2019

I worked as a Stagehand in this school's

SKILLS

- Kind
- Focused
- Strong Work Ethic
- Works with others comfortably
- Works independently comfortably
- Follows Instructions easily
- Problem Solving
- Troubleshooting
- Creative
- Orientation / Navigation

SKILLS (Technical)

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- Iava
- OOP
- PHP (Basic)
- MySQL
- MongoDB (Basic)
- NoSQL (Basic)
- Angular
- TypeScript
- Linux / Unix
- SpringBoot Framework

production of The Little Mermaid. Some of my tasks included being in charge of audio, lighting, building props, moving props, and managing the backstage.

Mariano's Pizza Brantford — General Worker

September 2023 - Present

I work here as a general worker, where I am in charge with taking orders, making pizzas, and ensuring customers receive hot and fresh product.

EDUCATION

Sheridan College, Oakville — *Computer Programming*

September 2022 - Present

I am in my last semester of Computer Programming and should be graduating by the middle of December.

Saint Ignatius of Loyola, Oakville — *High-School*

September 2018 - June 2022

REFERENCES

Available upon request.

- Python (Basic)
- C, C#
- .NET Framework
- .NET Core

AWARDS

- Graduated
 High-School with
 Honors.
- Technology Award.
- Computer Science Award.
- Award for competing in CanHack 2022 CyberSecurity Competition.

LANGUAGES

English